the largest republic was the RSFSR and
самая большая республика была РСФСР и
Chechnya was part of the RSFSR That is,
вот Чечня входила в состав РСФСР То есть
it was a unitary
это была унитарная
territory And in this territory
территория Вот и на этой территории
certain people seized power,
определённые люди захватили власть никем
not elected by anyone, just like you, not
не выбранные как никем не вым не
elected by anyone Look, you are
избранные как раз Смотрите вот вы
lying Look at the elections, Dzhakhar
обманываете Посмотрите выборы джахар
Dudayev was the elected president of Chechnya
Дудаев был избранным президентом Чечни
Look, there were
Посмотрите были
elections, really In what year
выборы правда В каком году
Great, where are you
Здорово вы
from, St. Petersburg, I understand I am from Latvia, the
откуда санкт-петербург понял Я из Латвии
city of Riga, we have been in
город Рига были у нас в
Latvia, no, I understand And what do you communicate about, never,
Латвии нет понял а чём общаетесь никогда
but different topics And by the way, in what countries
а разные темы А в каких кстати странах
were
были
interesting In Kazakhstan, I was in the near
интересны в Казахстане был в ближнем
abroad, mainly in Armenia, in
зарубежье в основном в Армении в
Turkey, in Egypt, this is not near Tunisia Well,
Турции в Египте это не ближне Тунис Ну
and in Europe, somewhere in Europe, for
так а в Европе где-то в Европе были для
you, the near abroad is Estonia
вас ближние зарубеж это Эстония
Finland Well, yes You can say so, but I have never
Финляндия Ну да Можно и так сказать но в
been to Finland, I took my brother to the border a couple of times and that's it And it is
Финляндию не ездил ни разу пару раз на
so
границу отвозил брата и всё А так
interesting And why was it not interesting what was
интересно А почему не интересно было что
there And what is interesting there Maybe it is the
там А что там интересно Может быть там
same there, in
тоже самое по
essence, I understood You have such an opinion about Europe as
сути понял У вас такое Европе мнение как
treat the fact that Russia is
относитесь к тому что Россия
Ukrainian as an inevitability
украино как к неизбежности
why Well, how else can you
почему Ну а как к этому ещё можно
treat it You know history well The
относиться Вы хорошо знаете историю
history of the last 30 years is bad I didn’t
Историю вот последних 30 лет плохо Я не
study history of the last 30 years at school
учил в школе историю последних 30 лет
Well, they don’t teach it at school for the last 30 years
Ну так последние 30 лет в школе и не
you just have to live
преподают это просто нужно жить Вам
How old are you 43
сколько лет 43
3 years older than me you
на 3 года старше меня вы в принципе
should basically know these events like me you
должны знать эти события кае меня вот
know specifically what I would like to
конкретно знаете что я хотел бы
focus your attention on the war in
сосредоточить Ваше внимание на войне в
Chechnya In Chechnya was there a
Чечне в Чечне разве была
war Of course there was no someone declared
война Конечно была нет кто-то объявлял
war how is it that is military action you
войну как это то есть боевые действия вы
were there a counter-terrorist
там была контртеррористическая
operation Well, you can say so avowedly
операция Ну можно и так сказать
and who can declare war well the
обяв а кто может объявить войну ну
Supreme Commander-in-Chief who do you have there
Верховный главнокомандующий кто там у
Yeltsin Well, it’s just
вас Ельцин Ну просто
how can I tell you Chechnya It was when the
это как вам сказать Чечня Она когда
Soviet Union collapsed
Советский Советский Союз распался
and the largest republic was the RSFSR and
и самая большая республика была РСФСР и
Chechnya was part of the RSFSR That is,
вот Чечня входила в состав РСФСР То есть
it was a unitary
это была унитарная
territory And in this
территория Вот и этой
territory certain people seized
территории определённые люди захватили
power not elected by anyone as not
власть никем не выбранные как никем не
elected by anyone just  look
выбра нием не избранные как раз смотрите
you are lying look at the elections dzhakhar
вы обманываете Посмотрите выборы джахар
Dudayev was the elected president of Chechnya
Дудаев был избранным президентом Чечни
look there were
Посмотрите были
elections true in what year now I will
выборы правда В каком году сейчас я вам
tell you in what year let's
скажу В каком году Давайте
say and the parliament was there so here are the
Скажите и Парламент там был Так вот
presidential elections were held in Chechnya on
президентские выборы прошли в Чечне 27
October 27, 1991
октября 1991 года
so these were not elections stop stop
так это это не были выборы
those let's read again
зах стоп стоп те Давай прочитай ещё раз
meaning seizure of power where do you
смысле захват власти вы вы это где
read this here I opened Wikipedia here I opened
читаете вот Википедии открыл вот я
Dudayev's elections Well Wikipedia Yeah well well
выборы Дудаева Ну Википедия Да ну так ну
look again let's see the presidential
посмотри ещ раз давай президентские
elections of the year in cheni last took place on
выборы де года в чени прош прошли 27
October 27 the winners of these elections were
октября победителям этих выборов был
porn hard at the same time elections to the
прон харда одновременно пошли выборы в
parliament of ichkeria went
парламент ичкери
on Wikipedia they write
в Википедии пишут
that ancient Ukrainian
что Древне украинско
[music]
[музыка]
gobya Find Look in other sources
гобя Найди Посмотри в других источниках
but there were elections dzhakhar Dudayev was the
но выборы были джахар Дудаев был
president of Ichkeria Yes there were
президентом Ичкерии Да не было там
no elections there as there were no elections
никаких выборов как не было выбо
look Google your sources
посмотри Погугли Сва своих источниках
on but there were no elections there was in
по но не было никаких выборов был по
fact a seizure of power  pozhe zna uste che
факту захват Вла поже зна усте че
vr Chechnya declared independence
вр Чечня провозгласила независимость
even Chechnya declared independence it
даже Чечня провозгласила независимость
left the USSR earlier than
она вы вышла из состава СССР раньше чем
Russia left the
Россия вышла из состава
USSR Russia signed in
СССР Россия подписала в
Belovo I tell you again that there
белове ещё раз вам говорю что выборов в
were no elections in Chechnya at all there was in fact a
Чечне не было вообще там был по факту
violent seizure of
силовой захват
power the
власти
voter there were polling stations
избиратель были избирательные участки бы
candidates there were elections official
кандидаты были выборы официальные
voting everything What candidates I
голосования всё Какие кандидаты я тебе
tell you again tell me how how was
ещё раз говорю вот скажи как как было
Chechen society organized once again once again
устроено чеченское общество ещё раз ещё
Chechen Chechen society was
раз чеченско чеченское общество было
secular Soviet secular society
светское Советское светское общество
was chu Well how not to have a secular society
было чу Ну как не надо светское общество
Yes everything is fine In 1991
Да нормально всё В девяносто первом году
when the Soviet Union was falling apart at the seams
когда Советский Союз трещал по швам
Republics declared independence
Республики провозглашали независимость
Yes Ichkeria also declared
Да Ичкерия тоже провозгласила
independence even before Russia even
независимость ещ до того как Россия даже
became independent yes Russia left the
стала независимой да Россия выходила из
USSR already without Ichkeria without Ichkeria no
состава СССР уже без Ичкерии без Ичкерии
one no one elected it there Well how did
никто никто его там не выбирал Ну как не
n't he elect well look at the
выбирал ну посмотри ещё ну как не
borders of the RSFSR look at the RSFSR
выбирал вот границ РСФСР посмотри РСФСР
look at the  once RSFSR Yes, this is an illegal
смотри ещё раз РСФСР Да это незаконное
state formation, everything was already
государственное образование уже было всё
like This is illegal The Soviet Union was
как Это незаконно Советский Союз
falling apart The Soviet Union was falling apart The
разваливался Советский Союз разваливался
republics declared independence
Республики провозглашали Независимости
Yes, Ichkeria declared
Да вот ичкери провозгласила
independence
независимость
declared Which republics Tastan
провозгласила Какие Республики тастан
declared as if there were no republics
провозгласил как не было республик
look Tell me all the republics in the
посмотри Назови мне все Республики в
Soviet Union once again in the RSFSR there was a
Советском Союзе ещё раз в РСФСР была
republic Chechen-Ingush ASSR
республика чечено-ингушская АССР
Autonomous Soviet Socialist
автономная Советская Социалистическая
Republic all this is a lie was unitary once
Республика всё это враньё был унитарна
again no No, you are deceiving You will deceive you will deceive You are
ещ раз не Нет ты обманываешь Ты обману
deceiving I look I was
ты обману Ты обманываешь я смотри я во
born in my first year I remember the children's
первого года рождения Я помню детский
atlas of the USSR in the USSR it is therefore
атлас ССР в ССР она поэтому и
Federal because it was not
Федеративная потому что она не была
unitary The FSR was not unitary it was a
унитарной ФСР не была унитарная это была
Federation Look in the RSFSR it was part of it was a
Федерация Посмотри в РСФСР входили это
territory Find me specifically here is a
была территория Вот найди мне конкретно
map how again Decipher What is the
вот кар как ещё раз Расшифруй Как
name deciphered RSFSR
называется расшифровывается РСФСР
Russian
Российская
Federal Soviet Federal
Федеративная совеская Федеративная
Republic yes that is Socialist
Республика да то Социалистическая
Republic that is Federal it is
Республика то есть Федеративная это
federa That's all that was included That's all that
федера Это всё что входило Это всё что
in fact was Russia Russia did not
по факту было россие России не было
exist the word Russia did not exist the word Russia did not
слова Россия не было слова Россия не
exist in the Soviet Union the word
было не было в Советском Союзе слова
Russia did not exist there was the RSFSR there was the UkrSSR Ukrainian
Россия не было было РСФСР было усср
Soviet Socialist
украинская Советская Социалистическая
Republic was the
Республика была
BS FSR No, once again in the FSR there were autonomous
БС ФСР Нет ещё раз в ФСР были автономные
republics as
Республики в
part of I told you specifically you said
составе Я тебе конкрет сказал ты сказал
that unita I'm telling you again the FSR was not unitary
что унита я е раз говорю ФСР не была
Of course unita that's the territory You
унита Конечно унита вот территория Ты
just
просто
if it has Federal in words if
если у неё Федеративная в словах если
it is Federal it is no longer unitary
она Федеративная она уже не унитарная
that's damn because Federal It was the
это блин потому что Федеративная Это был
status of the Republic itself you understand it was necessary to come out
статус самой Республики понимаешь выйти
as some kind of Republic
надо было в качестве какой-то Республики
no stop stop stop it did not come out as a
не стоп стоп стоп она не выходила в
federal It was created by
качестве федеративна Она и была создана
Lenin it was created by Lenin as a
ленином она она была создана ленином в
Federal Republic in short
качестве Федеративной Республики короче
in short you chu no Look I'm a lawyer I'm a lawyer
Короче ты чу нет Смотри Я юрист Я юрист
RSFSR it is Federal not unitary
РСФСР она Федеративная не унитарная
no elections don't run away again
никаких выборов во ещё раз не убегай
Come on now you're jumping for unita I
Давай сейчас за унита ты прыгаешь Я тебя
caught you now by elections now I caught you
поймал теперь по выборам теперь поймал
by unitarity  The RSFSR cannot be
по унитарность РСФСР не может быть
unitary because it is a federation,
унитарна потому что она Федеративная это
you are voicing it to yourselves, the RSFSR included
ж ты озвучиваешь своим в РСФСР входили
autonomous Soviet socialist
автономные советские социалистические
republics, for example,
республики например
now it is like the Chechen-Ingush Chechen-
сейчас она как чечено ингушка чечено
Ingush
ингушская
ASSR, yes, it was called the Chechen-
АССР вот есть да вот она называлась
Ingush Autonomous Soviet
чечено-ингушская автоном Советская
Socialist Republic, look also
Социалистическая Республика смотри также
and other ASSRs were included, other Republics
и другие АССР входили другие Республики
were part of the Russian Federation, this is
входили в состав Российской это уже
later, they appeared When already to when
позже они появились Когда уже ко когда
specifically They were given the status of a
уже конкретно Им дали статус
republic again, al Look, look again, the
рес ещё раз ал Вот смотри ещё раз
Chechen-Ingush USSR since
чечено-ингушская СССР с
1936, it has existed since 1936 Do you
1936 года она существует с 1936 года
hear? This was after this appeared
Слышишь Это после это уже появилось
after
после
No, I am telling you, here, open it, look You
Нет я тебе говорю вот Открой посмотри Ты
just had them even under Stalin, under Lenin,
их просто ещ при Сталине при Ленине
look at the Chechen-Ingush SSR When it
посмотри чечено-ингушская ССР Когда
appeared in the thirty-sixth year, look, I am writing a
появилась тридцать ше год смотри я пишу
map, a
карта
RS f SR, everything, and we are looking What is
РС ф СР всё и мы смотрим Что там
drawn there specifically, the territories Which ones
нарисовано конкретно территории Какие
go, everything, look at the composition, what are you
ходят всё посмотри состав что ты мне
telling me  here specifically separate
рассказываешь вот конкретно отдельные
separate Republics there were only 17
отдельные Республики было всего 17
republics and here specifically were those that had a
республик и вот были конкретно у которых
theoretical here just Well look
был теоретическая вот просто Ну смотри
take In any in any sources Type
возьми В любо в любом источники Набери
Chechen-Ingush ASSR in any I look
чечено ингушская АССР в любом я смотри
if you now If really earlier it was not I
если ты сейчас Если действительно раньше
admit Yes I admit let's
не было я признаю Да я признаю давай
look when it was formed in thirty-
посмотри когда она образована в тридцать
sixth
шестом
year Chechen-Ingush Autonomous
году чечено-ингушская автономная
Soviet Socialist
Советская Социалистическая
Republic existing from
Республика существующая с
1936 to forty-fourth And then Because
1936 по сорок четвёртый А дальше Потому
the war interrupted then from fifty-
что войной перервала потом с пятьдесят
seventh to ninety-first look so
седьмого по девяносто первый смотри так
year from fifty-seventh to ninety-
год с пятьдесят седьмого по девяносто
third that is to say to ninety-first from
третий вот то есть по девяносто первый с
ninety-first it was per No no no Look
девяносто первым она была пере Нет нет
you deceptions look
нет Смотри ты обманы смотри
in No from de to e from de to de it
в Нет с де по е с де по де она
proclaimed one hundred Chechen-Ingush USSR
провозгласила ста чечено ингушской СССР
look source What do you have Look here
смотри источник У тебя какой Смотри вот
I opened Wikipedia What are you
я Википедию открыл Ты что
opening I open specifically this
открываешь Я открываю конкретно это
what site now now I will
какой сайт сейчас сейчас
open This  definitely
открою Это точно
not good what did you open
нехорошо какой ты открыл
then Grozny m.ru what what is this
значит Грозный m.ru что что это вообще
what kind of site Grozny m.ru this is a site
что за сайт Грозный m.ru это сайт
specifically specific site where
конкретно конкретный сайт где
Chechen Whose site is this no no no no
чеченская Чей это сайт нет нет нет нет
look there may be something
смотри там может что
I don't know let's
хоче Я не знаю давай какой-то реально
take some real reference site Come on And what
справочный сайт возьмём Давай А что
is a reference Okay let's go Let's go
такое справочный Хорошо давай воз Давай
Stop let's take the great Russian
во Стоп давай возьмём большая российская
encyclopedia let's take pain wait knowledge
энциклопедия берём боль подожди знания
Russia ru I'll tell you let's open look let's
Россия ру я тебе скажу открываем смотри
open the official site the great
открываем официальный сайт большая
Russian encyclopedia it is
российская энциклопедия она официальным
made official by this Russian institute
этим институтом российским делается
Dava Well ninety-third year to
Дава Ну девяносто третий год по
ninety-third
девяносто Трей
year look I'm even opening
год вот смотри я сейчас даже открываю
Wikipedia now even in Wikipedia it is written
Википедию даже в Википедии это написано
you're lying just brazenly No you're
ты врёшь просто в наглую Нет ты
deceiving yes Look you've already lied I
обманываешь да Смотри ты уже соврал Я
dunked you because you said that the
тебя макнул потому что ты сказал что
Chechen SSR Appeared only in ninety-
чеченская ССР Появись только В девяносто
first after the collapse of the Union I told you
первом после развала Союза Я же говорил
that from thirty-sixth I  turned out to be right
Что С тридцать шестого я оказался прав
really I turned out to be right listen from
правда я оказался прав слышишь с
1936 to 1944 I told you
1936 по соро четвёртый год тебе сказал
then the war interrupted then from
потом войно перервала потом с пятьдесят
1957 then that is from 1957
седьмого потом то есть с пять седьмого
to 1990 Three then [ __ ] you said that
по девяносто Трей то сри ты сказал что
it appeared only after the collapse of the Union
она появилась только после развала Союза
You said it's true I said that from
Ты же сказал правда я сказал что С
1936 it's true that is I was in
тридцать шестого правда то есть я был
1911 the Union collapsed the
десто первом году Союз развал был развал
Union collapsed was in de I was right you said that
Союза был в де Я был прав ты сказал что
it appeared only after the collapse of the Union
она появилась только после развала Союза
You said I said that no it was from
Ты сказал Я сказал что нет она была С
1936 and you screamed screamed that no no no again to
тридцать шестого и Ты орал орал что нет
you again I
нет нет ещё раз тебе ещё раз я тебе
repeat to you look from
повторяю смотри с
1957 to de Trey year sing let's do it from
1957 по де Трей год поь давай так с
1957 it was from 1957 it was from
пятьдесят седьмого она была с пятьдесят
1957 it was true the Union collapsed
седьмого она была правда распался союз
When in 1991 in short listen
Когда В девяносто первом короче слушайте
I'm leaving now if you start again everything everything
Я сейчас ухожу если ты начинаешь ещё раз
because I drove you
ещё всё всё потому что я тебя загнал
Look I caught you with Dudayev's elections
Смотри Я тебя поймал с выборами Дудаева
I caught you with the fact that you said that
Я тебя поймал с тем что ты сказал что
Russia was a unitary state No
Россия была унитарное государство Нет
it  federal and I caught you with the fact
оно федеративное и я тебя поймал с тем
that you don't even know that the
что ты даже не знаешь да что
Chechen-Ingush ASSR was part of the
чечено-ингушская АССР было в составе
RSFSR yet elections in ch code don't run away
РСФСР ещё коно выборы в ч кода не убегай
No you jump from topic to topic No no no Let's do it
Нет ты прыгай с темы на тему Нет нет нет
again Look you let's
Давай ещё раз Смотри ты ты давай
record that you deceived all your
зафиксируем что ты обманул всех своих
viewers and mine Yes that the Chechen-Ingush
зрителей и моих Да что чечено-ингушская
SSR appeared only after the collapse of the
ССР появилась только после развала
Soviet Union No we you just
Советского Союза Нет мы ты только что
opened and confirmed with your lips that from
открыл и своими губами подтвердил что С
thirty-sixth to socha after the collapse of the
тридцать шестого по соче после развала
Soviet Union In ninety-third to
Советского Союза В девяносто треть по
ninety-third year until ninety-
девяносто третий год до девяносто
first it was it was everything that
первого была она она была была всё то
is the Chechen-Ingush SSS I'm telling you
есть чечено-ингушская ССС я тебе говорю
that federal federal status It
что федеральный федеральный статус Она
received this when after two Chechen
получила это когда после двух чеченских
yet no federal status it was it was
щё нет федеральный статус она была она
part of the Russian Federation would be
частью Российской Федерации бы
Federal Federal or
Федеративной Федеративной или
Federal
Федеральной
you look again in the RSFSR Yes all the
ты ещё раз смотри в РСФСР Да все
Republics had Federal
Республики имели Федеративный
status they are part of the Federation Ral is also a
статус они часть Федерации Раль это тоже
federal Yes federal
са федеральный Да федеральный
Federal or federal federal
Федеративный или федеральный федераль
it's all the same this word Union
это всё одно и то же это слово Союзный
translation it's the same Federation - it's
перево это одно и то же Федерация - это
translated as Union You definitely you definitely are a
в переводе Союз Ты точно ты точно это
lawyer definitely a lawyer then you're probably
юрист точно юрист то ю наверно
unemployed Yes definitely a lawyer but you've already been
безработный Да точно юрист а вот ты уже
caught you look you're running away now
пойман ты ты смотри ты сейчас убегаешь
want to run away again Yes and so look
хочешь снова убежать Да и значит смотри
let's do this subjects uh Russian
давай так субъекты ээ российской
Federal Soviet Federative
Федеративной Советской Федеративной
Socialist Republic what were
Социалистической Республики какие были
you wait you told me that it
ты погоди ты мне сказал что она до
existed until ninety-one I'm
девяносто первого существовала я тебе
showing you already in three IS again yes it
показываю уже в трёх ИС ещё раз да она
existed until ninety-one
существовала до девяносто первого потому
because in ninety-one the
что В девяносто первом была
republic of Ichkeria was proclaimed everything
провозглашена ээ республика Ичкерия всё
yes you look in those source You
да ты смотришь в тех источник Ты
look no it's Russia believed that
смотришь нет это Россия считала что
it existed as the cssr Ichkeria already
существует она как чсср Ичкерия уже
existed as an independent state
существовала как независимое государство
it Who recognized it And what's the difference who
она Кто её признал А какая разница кто
recognized Abkhazia someone recognized the DPR LPR
признал Абхазию кто-то признал ДНР лнр
someone can be but how can you Well
кто-то можно быть а как можно Ну вот
now look in Latvia now it will take Well
сейчас смотри в Латвии сейчас возьмёт Ну
so  look there were some there LNR DNR too
так посмотри так там лнр ДНР тоже
look Russia Russia Russia
какие-то были смотри Росси Россия Россия
controlled What flag was hanging there whose
контролировала Какой флаг там висел чей
flag was hanging there whose flag was hanging in Chechnya in
флаг там висел чей флаг висел в Чечне в
Ichkeria in
Ичкерии в
Grozny What flag was hanging there who was paying
Грозном Какой флаг там висел кто платил
pensions separatist separatist No well
пенсии сепаратист сепаратист Нет ну
wait a minute What episode official
подожди ты ка ты Какой эпизод официа
officially elected authorities were Dudayev
официально избранные власти были Дудаев
parliament of Ichkeria there were no
парламент ичкери не было там никаких
official Russia Russia paid
официальны Россия Россия платила там
pensions there Russia p Tell me the date when the
пенсии Россия п Назови мне дату когда
elections were held I told you I
были проведены выборы Я же тебе сказал я
told you October 27 ninety-one
тебе сказал 27 октября девяносто первого
I read it to you now I Wait a minute I
года я тебе прочитал сейчас я Погоди я
just don't have this this nonsense anywhere So
просто этого этого Бреда нигде нет Так
we Well on Google take Dudayev's elections
мы Ну на Гугле возьми выборы Дудаева Вот
Just take it on Google we started with this
возьми просто на Гугле мы же с этого
so there may be some nonsense there but
так там может быть какая-нибудь фигня но
not a choice Well take it again take it
не выбор Ну возьми ещё раз возьми ещё
again you're on Google you
раз ты же на Гугле ты с этого и
started with this so the thing is that you first have
начал так дело-то в том что ты сначала
some events then others and everything is complete
одни события потом другие и всё полный
nonsense look there is only in  Wikipedia
бред смотри есть есть только в Википедии
writes this nonsense and in all other
пишут этот бред а во всех остальных
sources there are no elections what
источниках нет никаких выборов каких
sources do you want
источников ты хочеть
Kadyrov is
Кадыров
recognized You just don't know how
признают Ты просто не знаешь как
Chechen society is structured it is
устроено чеченское общество там не
impossible to hold elections there look enter
возможно провести выбо смотри введи
Dudayev's elections in Google take no look look not
Дудаева возьми нет смотри смотри не
Wikipedia Find in any Yes I'll tell you
Википедию Найди в любом Да я тебе скажу
find Dudayev's elections take
най найди выборы Дудаева возьми выборы
Dudayev's elections enough this nonsense No no no
Дудаева хватит вот этот бред Нет нет нет
look take it on Google there were elections there were
смотри возьми на Гугле выборы были были
official elections there were
официальные выборы были участки
polling stations yes Russia you are silent
избирательные да Россия ты молчишь
come no Look E T You now you are
приходи нет Смотри Е Т Ты сечас ты
salt now you want to merge I got it you
сейчас соль ты хочешь слиться я понял ты
I caught you already on what republics it is impossible
Я тебя подловил уже на че республи
how impossible there
невоз возможно как невозможно вон
Kadyrov is elected everything noda and ruled kla
кадырово избирают всё нода и правили кла
everything is fine they elected
всё нормально избрали
Kadyrov look So we are recording yes the
Кадырова смотри Значит мы фиксируем да
Chechen Republic of Ichkeria
Чеченская республика Ичкерия
declared independence even before the
провозгласила независимость ещё до того
Russian Federation declared independence
Российская Феде
in Chechnya the presidential elections and elections were officially held
в Чечне был официально провен выборы
parliament were where
президента и выборы парламента были куда
ran away to what year
убежал до че года функционировали
all organs functioned absolutely normally Yes until
абсолютно нормально все органы Да пока
Russia invaded Ichkeria And it was a
Россия не вторглась в ичкери И это была
divine fire of
божественная пожаро
this First yes yes yes what
этого Сначала да да да какие
elections Federation unitary how can it
выборы Федерация унитарная как может
be
быть
because I don’t know jurisprudence
потому что это ж не знаю правоведение
ninth grade children are told look there are
девятый класс детям говорят вот смотрите
unitary states there are
есть унитарные государства есть
federal unitary federal if the
федеративные унитарные федеративные если
Russian Soviet Federative
Российская Советская Федеративная
Socialist Republic then how
Социалистическая Республика то как она
can it be unitary Well and then in general it
может быть унитарной Ну а дальше вообще
was yes no no no the Chechen-Ingur USSR appeared the Chechen-Ingur
было да нене не чсср появился чечено
USSR appeared in the day after the
ингурская СССР появилась в дено после
collapse googles and everything It was a
развала гуглит и всё Это был
Divine dressing down and Divine Escape of
Божественный разнос и Божественный Побег
this
этого
pseudo historian
э псевдо историка
pseudo like squeak comment We are fried in the
псевдо лайк писка комент Мы жари в
best letter on my Instagram I don’t know
найкраще пись на мий Instagram Я не знаю
why this is for what else tob there to
для чого це тоб для чого ще тоб там
watch on my face But for you this
дивитись на оцей мий фейс Але для тебе
is one two or three clicks But you are trimming
це один два або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I will roll Wow in  I have a lot of
мене и я буду катати Вау в мене там Купа
fouls there and I have a great mood to
фолов и в мене буде класный настрий щоб
make new cool videos Write to my
робити нове крут видео Пиши на мий
Instagram Popik Andriy
Instagram Попик Андрий
then Come on I'm
отак Давай я тебя
waiting for you L
чекаю L